Do you then sell or accept even then ...?
"I have 49 other companies, it gets rid of."
I can definitely sell.
If a company does something I disagree with.
But at the same time think ... that I should value it is better to sell than to keep-
-When the whole market says it is worth so much ... then I would rather stay.
The picture shows Warren Buffett selling stock-
-For SEK 135 billion in May this year.
A considerable sum even for him.
Everything is relative ...
He often argues that you should never sell, but still he did it himself.
What do you think he violates his mantra to never sell?
I think about what he said when he was a little younger ... that when he was very young-
-He had a lot of good ideas, but not so much money.
Now he has much more money-